<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Math Et al.</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Math Et al.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>Schedule for Spring 2024 Monday Tuesday Wednesday Thursday Friday 8 AM 9 AM 10 AM 11 AM Class Class Class Class 12 PM Office Hour Office Hour Office Hour Office Hour 1 PM Class Class Class Class 2 PM Office Hour 3 PM Meeting 4 PM Meeting Office - BH 115J&#xA;Address - 3201 Campus Drive, Klamath Falls, OR 97601&#xA;Email - dibyajyoti.deb[at]oit[dot]edu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interests</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interests/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/research/</guid>
      <description>My research interests are in number theory. More specifically my work involves Diophantine equations, p-adic and algebraic number theory. I am also interested in the theory of Quadratic forms.&#xA;Currently, I am a Professor of Mathematics at the Oregon Institute of Technology. Before coming here, I was a Visiting Assistant Professor in the Department of Mathematics at the University of Toledo, OH from 2010 to 2013. I completed my Ph.D. in Mathematics from the University of Kentucky in August 2010, under the supervision of Prof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/</guid>
      <description>SPRING 2024 Classes that I am teaching this term:&#xA;MATH 254 - Vector Calculus I MATH 341 - Linear Algebra I Check Canvas for course details and information.&#xA;Some old course notes written by me&#xD;Differential Calculus Integral Calculus Differential Equations Some old videos that I made&#xD;Vector Calculus I Mathematical Structures Differential Equations Discrete Mathematics Linear Algebra I Linear Algebra II Vector Calculus II Courses that I have taught in the past&#xD;Oregon Institute of Technology (2013 -) Intermediate Algebra, College Algebra, Trigonometry, Differential Calculus, Integral Calculus, Sequences and Series, Vector Calculus I, II, Applied Differential Equations I, II, Linear Algebra I, II, Mathematical Structures, Introduction to Real Analysis, Number Theory, Discrete Mathematics, Applied PDE I, Numerical Methods I, II, III, Mathematical Statistics.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
